<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Orcutt</title><link>http://johnorcutt.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Orcutt</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 22:48:37 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://johnorcutt.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>20230129</title><link>http://johnorcutt.github.io/posts/20230129/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 22:48:37 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://johnorcutt.github.io/posts/20230129/</guid><description>Why have I started a blog in 2023, over a decade after blogs stopped being a thing that individuals have? Well, the story isn&amp;rsquo;t super interesting, but I always felt limited by the few hundred characters that I could post on Twitter. Additionally the culture over there seemed to be mostly snark, dunks, arguments, and hatred. After all of the recent-ish events that have happened at twitter I could no longer use the service.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://johnorcutt.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://johnorcutt.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hi! 👋 I&amp;rsquo;m John Orcutt, a systems/software engineer building platforms for weather and climate modeling.
I&amp;rsquo;m located in the Longmont, Colorado which is situated in the Front Range region of the state. I&amp;rsquo;ll use my blog to share my thoughts on things I find interesting and am passionate about. You can also follow me on Mastodon. I intentionally am not going to allow comments here, but you can always reply or comment about my posts over on Mastodon.</description></item><item><title>Colophon</title><link>http://johnorcutt.github.io/colophon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://johnorcutt.github.io/colophon/</guid><description>Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;ve shamelessly stolen this from John Gruber&amp;rsquo;s wonderful Daring Fireball. I love the idea of having a place to share the technologies and tools you&amp;rsquo;re using and couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist.
Posts are written in Markdown using BBEdit. The site is powered by Hugo and I&amp;rsquo;m using the Paper theme. The site is deployed on GitHub Pages. More to come as I think of it&amp;hellip;</description></item></channel></rss>